dubbedanime.tk 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
Dubbed Anime is committed to protecting your privacy to allow for a safe and secure experience. This privacy policy outlines how information is collected and used. As our content and services constantly evolve we may modify this policy from time to time.

**Information Collection**  
We may collect information from you in order for you to use our services. This can include, but is not limited to your name, email address, and Internet Protocol address. Aside from your name or chosen nickname, other information will not be publicly available to others. We do not promote nor send spam thus we will not redistribute your information to any third parties.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
We may collect cookies from your computer depending on your preferences. Cookies are plain text files that are stored on your computer generally used to serve to your convenience for future visits. This can prevent repeatedly performing tasks such as typing in your name or email address each time by saving this information for future use. You can stop accepting cookies by configuring the settings in your browser, however, you may not be able to fully use the website features.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Obligation to Children’s Privac** y  
We never collect or maintain information from those who we actually know are under 13 years of age. Such information will be deleted if we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information.  
How to Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please use the contact email provided on the website to bring to our attention your concern.

Contact: dubbedanimexyz@gmail.com
